The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
It's my doll !
Let me play with it for a while...
Try to catch me then !
All of you, stop right there.
Who allowed you to come over here ?
Don't disturb the Celestial's cultivation.
Understood !
The Celestial hasn't shown himself for 3 months...
I wonder what he's doing.
Refining a Soul Flag is relatively easy.
That makes it suitable for the tribe members to learn.
Even without spiritual energy,
if they cultivate these techniques with demonic energy,
we might get unexpected results.
Go inside !
This Soul Flag made from redwood and beast hide
is way weaker than a true Soul Flag
but is simple to craft.
The tribe members will be able to protect themselves with it.
No matter how long someone refines the souls they capture
with the modified Soul Refining spell,
I'll be able to control them
with a single thought.
The stronger the tribe becomes,
the more Soul Flags I will control.
In this way,
I can also use this opportunity
to refill the Billion-Soul Flag.
With the Billion-Soul Flag,
I'll be more confident
in obtaining an Ancient Demon Spirit.
Celestial...
Do you really mean
to impart this technique to me ?
Not just you.
All tribe members
must practice this technique from now on.
Immortal,
even if Junior has heard of these objects,
I don't know how to use it.
Put it on your forehead.
Clear your mind and comprehend it.
This...
There's nothing at all ?
Blocked meridians
and poor talent.
No wonder he can't sense it...
Concentrate
and endure the pain.
Junior can see it now !
You will find inside the method to craft a Soul Flag and the Soul Refining spell.
You must memorize them carefully.
From now on,
you must teach them to everyone.
Ouyang Hua
will never forget Celestial's kindness !
Quick, quick, quick !
Be careful, everyone.
Over here, over here !
The rank 3 Demon Spirit Crystal
is complete.
This demonic energy is pretty interesting.
Unfortunately, I don't have enough of it,
just the equivalent of a Foundation Establishment cultivator.
After the Patriarch,
Thirteen was the first to successfully refine a Soul Flag !
This Soul Flag looks so impressive !
Brother Thirteen is amazing !
Little Thirteen,
even if you refined the Soul Flag,
you still need to refine souls and seal them inside.
You mustn't be arrogant nor impatient.
Now,
let's all help Thirteen hunt beasts
to help him extract their souls.
Who said I don't have souls ?
Watch closely !
So powerful !
Wh...What kind of demon beast is this !?
This is...
a Winged Mane Lion !
Attack !
How did you subdue
such a powerful demon beast ?
When I went hunting outside the valley,
I encountered this beast that had just died.
I silently recited the mantra taught by the Celestial
and actually managed to extract its soul
and seal it inside this Soul Flag !
Withdraw !
Return !
Damn beast !
Thank you Celestial for saving my life !
Remember,
the Soul Refining spell
has no shortcuts.
Although you sealed this beast by chance,
if your cultivation is too low,
you will suffer a backlash.
This child is actually pretty talented.
With just this little guidance, he seems to have understood.
He could achieve great things
if he matures a bit.
Celestial,
There are 27 members in the tribe.
Currently, besides me and Thirteen who have primary soul in our Soul Flags,
most of the others are still diligently practicing.
Celestial,
now that outsiders have entered our land,
a new round of tribe wars
to plunder resources
is about to begin, as it did in the past.
Our days ahead
are going to be rough.
Rather than waiting to be attacked,
we should strike first !
Since we have no way to escape these conflicts,
why don't we strengthen ourselves as quickly as possible ?
Celestial,
I wish to mobilize the tribe members
to invade an underground cave 1000 li away.
It's inhabited by another tribe
with several dozen members.
The Soul Refining spell I gave you
grants you the freedom to act.
Cave Tribe
Go !
Surrender immediately
and you won't be killed !
Hurry up !
Keep up !
Don't fall behind !
The memory-wiping soup
makes them forget their past
to be reborn as a new tribe member.
Although this soup is useless on cultivators,
it's miraculous on the natives.
In this way,
the tribe expands
and more people can practice the Soul Refining spell.
This battle...
was worth it.
I pay respects to the Celestial !
I pay respects to the Celestial.
Celestial,
this is the Demon Spirit Crystal Junior found in the other tribe.
I offer it to you, Celestial.
Offering a Demon Spirit Crystal
counts as an achievement.
This is the mantra for the next stage.
Study it well
and don't teach it to others.
Thirteen will repay
Celestial's kindness with his life !
Thirteen is favored by the Celestial,
the future surely belongs to him.
Our small tribe
will eventually live in prosperity.
These old bones of mine
are glad.
Look, they're leaving !
Thirteen and the others are so impressive !
Whenever Brother Thirteen goes out,
we always have meat on our plates in the evening !
It seems like
this was the right move.
3 months later
Thirteen's squad
should have returned 2 days ago.
Little Thirteen !
You...
Celestial !
Thirteen, he...
His meridians are shattered,
his cultivation is ruined.
Celestial...
What happened ?
We were ambushed by a large tribe named the Tianshui Tribe.
All of my squad
was killed.
The white-robed elder leading them
took my Soul Flag
and planted a demon inside me.
He said if you want the Soul Flag back,
you must go to the Tianshui Tribe to find him.
Take him to rest.
Be careful, Celestial !
The Tianshui Tribe
is the most powerful tribe outside Ancient Demon City.
They are entrenched within an ancient formation
that was unshaken for thousands of years.
Thirteen
is a living challenge letter the Tianshui Tribe sent me.
Tianshui Tribe
Coming up !
Make way, make way !
Coveting his spells is one thing
but you crippled his cultivation too ?
Xie Hao
Tianshui Tribe Leader
Rank 1000 demonic energy
(Nascent Soul)
Doing this...
is a bit excessive.
Zeng Wei
Tianshui Tribe member
Rank 10 000 demonic energy
(Soul Formation)
I am under the Left Wing General.
How could killing a few savages
be called excessive ?
The technique that kid had was pretty interesting.
Unfortunately, it's incomplete.
If the one behind him doesn't dare to show up,
I will go to that small tribe tomorrow
and retrieve the full technique myself.
There's always a higher mountain.
This is still too risky...
Patriarch,
you've grown senile !
If that person was truly that skilled,
why wouldn't they join the army of Ancient Demon City ?
How could they possibly dwell in a small tribe ?
Moreover, our Tianshui Tribe has lasted thousands of years.
If we really provoked someone powerful,
we still have the ancient formation to guard us.
We're completely safe.
The one who issued the challenge letter
can come out !
An outsider !?
A Soul Transformation cultivator !
It's you...
Yes,
it was this old man who took those little flags.
If you wish to make me pay
then break the formation and come in !
Our Tianshui Tribe has lasted for thousands of years.
Even if you have heaven-defying abilities,
this formation
isn't something you can break !
I advise you to scram immediately
and stop making a fool of yourself !
This formation
can actually absorb attacks to become stronger.
Over time,
it naturally became indestructible.
Or is it ?
Wh..
What the hell is he doing !?
Rise !
Look who you've provoked !
A madman...
He's a madman !
Breaking the formation will take some time.
But refining you along with the formation
is pretty easy.
That's...
the Celestial !
If you insist on not coming out,
I will refine you for 7 days and 7 nights.
By then, your Tianshui Tribe
will have suffered the consequences.
We pray to Celestial's divine might !
Celestial...
Don't implicate the entire tribe
in the trouble you created !
Fellow cultivator,
I was the one who issued the challenge.
Do you dare fight me one-on-one ?
Don't involve the innocents !
You're not qualified.
Open the formation.
Ouyang Hua,
we have new tribe members.
The tribe is growing
thanks to Celestial's divine might !
We humbly request Celestial to bestow a new name upon our tribe
to grant us a new beginning.
Little friend Ceng Niu,
this old man
has one last request.
The tribe shall be named...
the Soul Refining Tribe.
The clouds and the mist cannot hide a thousand mountains.
This wish has remained unchanged for thousands of years.
The Dao can be condensed into a single thought.
The past flashes before my eyes
as I turn around to let it go.
Resolutely carrying the torch forward.
Even though the cycle of reincarnation is endless,
I have no regrets in my heart.
Only when facing death
does one realize they have no regrets.
I will fulfill your wish,
I will rush forward through dust and smoke to chase the light.
Even if the road is difficult,
I will give it my heart and soul.
Behind you, countless clear eyes
look at the world you made.
You soul will not die,
it will live forever.
I hold in my heart
your wish to bring back your past glory.
There will always be someone
to see the world you protected.
Even if it takes countless lifetimes.
Seeing mountains and rivers is like meeting people.
Let me carry on all the wishes
that you couldn't fulfill.
Fulfilling your wish